Guide to the Beer Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WILLIAM COLLINS BEER, 1880-1917; Series II; 15.6' (38 boxes)
  - Personal Files
    - photographs: Russell A. Alger, Edwin B. Babbitt, undated (Box 92, Folder 440)
    - photographs: William Beer, John B. Bellinger, Robert G. Cousins, undated (Box 92, Folder 441)
    - photographs: Charles G. Dawes, Wright P. Edgerton, Dudley Evans, Clarence S. Funk, J. M. Govin, undated (Box 92, Folder 442)
    - photographs: Marcus A. Hanna, M. Haskell, John Hay, Andrew Johnson, undated (Box 92, Folder 443)
    - photographs: John J. McCook, Abner McKinley, undated (Box 92, Folder 444)
    - photographs: William McKinley, Joseph Hopkins Millard, Benjamin F. Montgomery, Tommaso Mosca, undated (Box 92, Folder 445)
    - photographs; George W. Perkins, Reed Smoot, Henry D. Styer, Palmer W. West, Julius Whiting, Jr., Nicola [Zalioni?], undated (Box 93, Folder 446)
    - photographs: Council Bluffs, Iowa: Officer and Pusey Bank and the high school football team, undated (Box 93, Folder 447)
    - photographs; Manila, With captions by Robert C. Baldwin, Circa 1900 (Box 93, Folder 448)
    - photographs: Presidential campaign, 1896 (Box 93, Folder 449)
    - photographs: unidentified (Box 93, Folder 450)
    - programs, 1882-1905, 1911-1912, undated (Box 93, Folder 451-452)
    - scrapbook of European trip, 1913-1914 (Box 93, Folder 451-452)
      See: Folio Box II
    - sketch in pencil of unidentified subject, undated (Box 93, Folder 453)
    - societies and clubs: memoranda, 1903-1913 (Box 93, Folder 454)
    - miscellaneous memorabilia, 1894, 1904, undated (Box 93, Folder 455)
    - biographical information, 1886-1916, undated (Box 93, Folder 456)
- THOMAS BEER, 1897-1947; Series III; 12.7' (32 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer. Letters written by Thomas Beer are filed under the name of the addressee. General correspondence concerning publication of and rights to his writings, invitations and letters of condolence are filed at the end of the section.
  The material in Published Writings is arranged chronologically under the following categories: Books, Short Stories, Articles and Book Reviews, Poems, and Letters from Readers.
  The material in Unpublished Writings is arranged alphabetically under the following categories: Books, Short Stories, Articles and Book Reviews, Plays And Movie Scenarios, and Juvenilia.
  - editorial comments by Alice B. Beer on Thomas Beer's army correspondence (1917-1919), on his correspondence with various friends, and on his work habits, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    See also: box 124, folder 454
  - "Patchwork." Reminiscences by Alice Baldwin Beer about her family, with emphasis on the biography of her brother, Thomas, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - record kept by Alice Baldwin Beer of her work on the papers of Thomas Beer, n. d. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1910-1940 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Abbott, Cary, 1910-1930, n. d. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      To/From: 15/24
    - Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1916-1924 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      To/From: 6/0
    - B, 1908-1932 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      To/From:
    - Babbitt, Edwin B., 1917-1922 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      To/From: 3/0
    - Bellows, Emmas (Story): note with original sketch by George Wesley Bellows, undated (Box 94, Folder 8)
      To/From: 1/0
    - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Bernstein, Aline, 1923-1933, n. d. (Box 94, Folder 9)
      To/From: 4/0
    - Boyd, Ernest and Madeleine (Reynier), 1923-1933 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      To/From: 2-1/15
    - Boyd, Thomas (Alexander), 1925 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck., 1920-1923, n. d. (Box 94, Folder 11)
      See also: box 100, folder 91
    - Brown, Charles, 1906-1907 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - C, 1909-1931 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Cabell James Branch, 1922-1926, n. d. (Box 94, Folder 13)
      To/From: 5/5
    - Canby, Henry Seidel, 1923-1934 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      To/From: 9/0
    - Cather, Willa, undated (Box 94, Folder 13)
      To/From: 2/0
    - Cavendish Hotel and dog Kippy, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
      See also: box 109, folder 234
    - Collinge, Patricia, 1934-1935, undated (Box 94, Folder 15)
      To/From: 7/0
    - Colophon, The, 1929-1936 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Conrad, Joseph., 1923 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      See also; box 100, folder 91
    - Costain, Thomas Bertram.
      See: box 96, folder 49
    - [Cowan, Samuel Kinkade?], undated (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Craig, Channing, 1907-1908 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Crane, Edith., 1906-1939
      See: box 100, folder 91
    - D, 1906-1939 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Dana, John Cotton. (Box 95, Folder 17)
      See; box 100, folder 91
    - Davis, J. Frank, 1922 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - DeLong, [T.?], 1908-1925 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      To/From: 11/0
    - E, 1906-1930 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Elihu Club, The, 1910-1915, 1924-1939 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Ely, David Jay, 1910-1913, undated (Box 95, Folder 21)
      To/From: 18/0
    - F, 1910-1936 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Fair, James H, S, and Mary, 1906-1911, undated (Box 95, Folder 23)
      To/From: 27-4/0
    - Fisher, Helen Dwight, 1919-1927, undated (Box 95, Folder 24)
      To/From: 2/4
    - Fitzgerald, F. Scott, [1926], undated (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Follett, Wilson, 1923-1934 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Frank, Waldo, 1917, undated (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - G, 1922-1938 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Gammell, Arthur A., 1911-1912 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Garland, Hamlin., undated (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Garnett, Edward, 1924 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Glasgow, Ellen Anderson Gholson, 1932 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - H, 1908-1933 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Haight, James A., 1909-1939 (Box 95, Folder 28)
      To/From: 5/0
    - Harris, Arthur Ringland, 1933, undated (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Herzberg, Max J.
    - Hopkins, Charles Robert, 1913-1923 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Housum, Robert, 1919-1936, undated (Box 95, Folder 30)
      To/From: 13/14
    - Hughes, Rupert, 1921-1924 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Huidekoper, Frederic Louis, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Huston, McCready, 1924 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - I-J-K, 1910-1931 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche W., 1921-1938, undated (Box 95, Folder 33)
      To/From: 16-17/2
    - L, 1907-1938 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Leonhauser, Watson, 1907-1908 (Box 95, Folder 35)
      To/From: 12/0
    - Lockwood, Arthur J., 1901-1903 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      To/From: 0/3
    - Lombardi, Cornelius E., 1912-1925 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      To/From: 8/0
    - Lorimer, George Horace.
    - M, 1906-1941 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Mackenzie School, The, 1907-1908 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - Mencken, H(enry) L(ouis), 1936, undated (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Minnigerode, Meade, 1910-1926 (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Moley, Raymond, 1933-1934 (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Morley, Christopher, 1916-1924 (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - Mumford, Lewis, 1927-1940 (Box 96, Folder 40)
      To/From: 16/1
    - N-O, 1911-1939 (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - Norris, Charles Gilman and Kathleen (Thompson), 1926-1929 (Box 96, Folder 42)
      To/From: 1-1/0
    - Ober, Harold, 1934-1937 (Box 96, Folder 42)
      To/From: 14/0
    - O'Brien, Edward J., 1917-1926 (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - P, 1907-1938 (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - Pemberton, Brock, 1922, undated (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1911-1934 (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - Pigott, William T. and Maie, 1911-1923, 1936 (Box 96, Folder 44)
      To/From: 9-1/0
    - R, 1909-1937 (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - Reynolds, Paul R., 1922-1928 (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - Riggs, T. Lawrason, 1910, 1922, 1933, undated (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - Robinson, Henry A., Jr., 1907-1908 (Box 96, Folder 47)
      To/From: 15/0
    - Ross, Sanford, 1936, undated (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - S, 1907-1940 (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1916-1939 (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - Simmons, Edward, 1926 (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - Soule, George Henry, Jr., 1914, undated (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - Starrett, Vincent.
    - Street, Julian, 1922-1933 (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - Strout, E. A., Jr., 1910-1912 (Box 96, Folder 51)
      To/From: 4/1
    - Swinnerton, Frank Arthur and Mary (Bennett), 1928-1939 (Box 96, Folder 51)
      To/From: 2-3/0
    - T-U-V, 1917-1939 (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - Tarkington, Booth, 1919-1922 (Box 96, Folder 53)
    - Tener, Alexander C., 1910-1939 (Box 96, Folder 54)
      To/From: 20/0
    - Thompson, Charles Willis, 1931 (Box 96, Folder 55)
    - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1925-1936, undated (Box 96, Folder 55)
    - Toohey, John Peter., 1921-1925, undated (Box 96, Folder 55)
      See also: box 118, folder 395 See also: box 119, folder 403
    - Tuttle, H. Emerson, 1928 (Box 96, Folder 55)
    - United States Army, 1917-1919, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 56)
    - Vanderpoel, Abbott August, 1911-1912 (Box 96, Folder 57)
    - W, 1907-1940 (Box 96, Folder 58)
    - Walpole, Hugh, 1922-1923 (Box 96, Folder 59)
    - Wells, H. G.
    - Wheeler, Alexander Royal, 1909-1918, undated (Box 96, Folder 60)
      To/From: 40/l
    - Wheeler, William Reginald, 1910-1918, 1932-1937 (Box 97, Folder 61)
      To/From: 24/0
    - Wildman, Murray Shipley, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 62)
    - Wiley, Hugh, 1927 (Box 97, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Jesse Lynch, 1925-1926 (Box 97, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Wayland Wells, 1910-1916, 1938, undated (Box 97, Folder 63)
      To/From: 28/0
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 64)
    - Wilson, Harry Leon, 1922-1923 (Box 97, Folder 64)
    - Woollcott, Alexander, 1936 (Box 97, Folder 64)
    - Woolley, Edgar Montillion, 1906-1910 (Box 97, Folder 65)
    - Woolley, Edgar Montillion, 1911-1939 (Box 97, Folder 66)
      To/From: 19/12
    - Yale College, 1907-1940 (Box 97, Folder 67)
    - Yale College: organizations, 1910-1936 (Box 97, Folder 68)
    - correspondence with publishers, 1913-1939 (Box 97, Folder 69)
    - correspondence concerning subsidiary rights for publication of Beer's works in anthologies and in translation, 1923-1939 (Box 97, Folder 70)
    - correspondence concerning motion picture and dramatic rights for Beer's works, 1922-1935 (Box 97, Folder 71)
    - invitations, 1905-1932, undated (Box 97, Folder 72-73)
    - letters of condolence, A-D, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 74)
    - letters of condolence, F-H, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 75)
    - letters of condolence, I-P, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 76)
    - letters of condolence, Q-Z, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 77)
    - unidentified, 1906-1938, undated (Box 98, Folder 78)
  - Published Writings
    - "The Work of Thomas Beer: Appraisal and Bibliography:" dissertation by E. B. Harrington, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 79)
    - notes by Thomas Beer, undated (Box 98, Folder 80)
    - Books
      - The Fair Rewards. Typescript, 1922 (Box 98, Folder 81-83)
      - The Fair Rewards. Galley proofs corrected by Thomas Beer, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 84)
      - The Fair Rewards. Page proofs of preliminary pages and of introduction, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 85)
      - The Fair Rewards. Page proofs, with corrections by Thomas Beer, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 86)
      - The Fair Rewards. Page proofs, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 87)
      - The Fair Rewards. Plate proof, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 88)
      - The Fair Rewards. Publicity, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 89)
      - The Fair Rewards. Reviews, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 90)
      - Stephen Crane. Notes by Alice Beer (Box 100, Folder 91)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence A-D, 1922-1924 (Box 100, Folder 92)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence F-H, 1922-1924 (Box 100, Folder 93)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence L-P, 1922-1939 (Box 100, Folder 94)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence R-Z, 1922-1924 (Box 100, Folder 95)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence with Edith Crane, 1922-1934, undated (Box 100, Folder 96)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence with John Cotton Dana, 1922-1923 (Box 100, Folder 97)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence with Max J. Herzberg, 1922-1924 (Box 100, Folder 98)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence with Edna Ritchie Jones, 1923-1924 (Box 100, Folder 99)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence with Vincent Starrett, 1922-1928 (Box 100, Folder 100)
      - Stephen Crane. Correspondence re: Conrad preface, 1923-1937 (Box 100, Folder 101)
      - Stephen Crane. Research notes (Box 100, Folder 102-103)
      - Stephen Crane. Research notes: copies of letters by Stephen and Cora Crane (Box 100, Folder 104)
      - Stephen Crane. Typescript drafts, 1923 (Box 100, Folder 105-106)
      - Stephen Crane. Typescript corrected by Thomas Beer, 1923 (Box 100, Folder 107)
      - Stephen Crane. Introduction by Joseph Conrad; typescript and galley proof (Box 101, Folder 108)
      - Stephen Crane. Sketches and proofs of preliminary leaves, chapter headings (Box 101, Folder 109)
      - Stephen Crane. Galley proofs corrected by Thomas Beer, 1923 (Box 101, Folder 110)
      - Stephen Crane. Page proofs corrected by Thomas Beer, 1923 (Box 101, Folder 111)
      - Stephen Crane. Page proofs, 1923 (Box 101, Folder 112)
      - Stephen Crane. Plate proofs, 1923 (Box 102, Folder 113)
      - Stephen Crane. Publicity, 1923 (Box 102, Folder 114)
      - Stephen Crane. Reviews, 1923-1924 (Box 102, Folder 115-116)
      - Stephen Crane. Posthumous references. For inquiries by writers re: Stephen Crane papers, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 117)
        See also: box 12, folder 7 See also: box 12, folder 32 See also: box 127, folder 62 See also: box 127, folder 63
      - Sandoval. Holograph drafts (fragments), 1924 (Box 102, Folder 118)
      - Sandoval. Typescript, 1924 (Box 102, Folder 119-120)
      - Sandoval. Typescript, carbon copy, 1924 (Box 102, Folder 121)
      - Sandoval. The Saturday Evening Post installments: galley proof and printed pages, 1923 (Box 102, Folder 122)
      - Sandoval. Sketches and proofs of preliminary pages, 1924 (Box 102, Folder 123)
      - Sandoval. Page proofs, 1924 (Box 102, Folder 124)
      - Sandoval. Page proofs, 1924 (Box 103, Folder 125-127)
      - Sandoval. Plate proofs, 1924 (Box 103, Folder 128)
      - Sandoval. Publicity, 1924 (Box 103, Folder 129)
      - Sandoval. Reviews, 1924 (Box 103, Folder 130)
      - The Mauve Decade. Incomplete, typescript, 1926 (Box 103, Folder 131)
      - The Mauve Decade. Galley proofs, 1926 (Box 103, Folder 132)
      - The Mauve Decade. Publicity, 1926 (Box 103, Folder 133)
      - The Mauve Decade. Reviews, 1926-1927 (Box 103, Folder 134)
      - The Mauve Decade. Armed Services paperback edition vintage paper back edition with introduction by Franle Freidel, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 135)
      - The Road to Heaven. Drafts (incomplete), 1928 (Box 103, Folder 136)
      - The Road to Heaven. Typescript with corrections by Thomas Beer and others, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 137)
      - The Road to Heaven. Page proofs with corrections by Thomas Beer, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 138)
      - The Road to Heaven. Plate proofs and sketches and lay-outs for preliminary leaves, 1928. (Box 104, Folder 139)
      - The Road to Heaven. Publicity, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 140)
      - The Road to Heaven. Reviews, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 141)
      - Hanna. Research notes, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 142)
      - Hanna. Transcript of a conversation between Thomas Beer and his publishers, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 143)
      - Hanna. Manuscript fragments, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 144)
      - Hanna. Typescript with corrections by Thomas Beer and others, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 145)
      - Hanna. Galley proofs and printed pages of installments, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 146)
      - Hanna. Page proofs with corrections by Thomas Beer, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 147)
      - Hanna. Page proofs, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 148)
      - Hanna. Plate proofs of the introduction, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 149)
      - Hanna. Publicity, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 150)
      - Hanna. Reviews, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 151)
      - Mrs. Egg and Other Barbarians. Galley proofs with corrections by Thomas Beer, 1933 (Box 105, Folder 152)
      - Mrs. Egg and Other Barbarians. Page proofs, 1941 (Box 105, Folder 153)
      - Hanna, Crane, and the Mauve Decade. Galley proofs, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 154)
      - Hanna, Crane, and the Mauve Decade. Page proofs, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 155)
      - Hanna, Crane, and the Mauve Decade. Page proofs, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 156-157)
      - Hanna, Crane, and the Mauve Decade. Publicity, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 158)
      - Hanna, Crane, and the Mauve Decade. Reviews, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 159)
    - Short Stories
      - Bibliography of published stories, catalog and synopses by Alice Beer (Box 106, Folder 160)
      - "King's Evil", 1908 March (Box 106, Folder 161)
      - "The Pantamorph", 1908 October (Box 106, Folder 162)
      - "One Way of Death", 1909 February (Box 106, Folder 163)
      - "Alms for Oblivion", 1909 March (Box 106, Folder 164)
      - "Orchids", 1909 April (Box 107, Folder 165)
      - "Sleeping Dogs", 1909 May (Box 107, Folder 166)
      - "Beatus Ille", 1909 October (Box 107, Folder 167)
      - "The Cat", 3910 January (Box 107, Folder 168)
      - "The Freshman of Feeling", 1911 March (Box 107, Folder 169)
      - "The Brothers", 1917 February (Box 107, Folder 170)
      - "Onnie", 1917 May (Box 107, Folder 171)
      - "The Rescuer", 1917 August 11 (Box 107, Folder 172a)
      - "Absent Without Leave", 1918 July 20 (Box 107, Folder 172b)
      - "Beneficiary", 1918 August (Box 107, Folder 172c)
      - "Jellyfish", 1919 May 10 (Box 107, Folder 173a)
      - "Old Men's Peace", 1919 June 14 (Box 107, Folder 173b)
      - "The House of Atreus", 1919 July (Box 107, Folder 174a)
      - "Lorena", 1919 October 25 (Box 107, Folder 174b)
      - "The Curious Behavior of Myra Cates", 1919 October (Box 107, Folder 174c)
      - "The Totem", 1919 November 29 (Box 107, Folder 175)
      - "Zerbetta and the Black Arts", 1919 December 6 (Box 107, Folder 176)
      - "The Boy Flag", 1920 June 5 (Box 107, Folder 177a)
      - "The Poison Pen", 1920 July 17 (Box 107, Folder 177b)
      - "Cool", 1920 September (Box 107, Folder 178a)
      - "Josh and the Lofty Mountain", 1921 January 29 (Box 107, Folder 178b)
      - "Little Eva Ascends", 1921 April 9 (Box 107, Folder 179a)
      - "The Lily Pond", 1921 April 16 (Box 107, Folder 179b)
      - "Mummery", 1921 July 30 (Box 108A, Folder 180a)
      - "The Yawl", 1921 August 6 (Box 108A, Folder 180b)
      - "Addio", 1921 October 29 (Box 108A, Folder 18Oc)
      - "Don Carlos Vittori", 1922 January 21 (Box 108A, Folder 180)
      - "The Citizens of Hidj", 1922 March 18 (Box 108A, Folder 181)
      - "Rope", 1922 March 25 (Box 108A, Folder 182)
      - "Balliol", 1922 May 13 (Box 108A, Folder 183a)
      - "The Enemy", 1922 May (Box 108A, Folder 183b)
      - "Tact", 1922 July 1 (Box 108A, Folder 184a)
      - "By Parables", 1922 August 26 (Box 108A, Folder 184b)
      - "Lips", 1922 September 9 (Box 108A, Folder 185a)
      - "Casual", 1922 September 20 (Box 108A, Folder 185b)
      - "Fifty and Fifty", 1922 September (Box 108A, Folder 185c)
      - "Virtue Rewarded", 1922 November 4 (Box 108A, Folder 185)
      - "Shock", 1922 December 9 (Box 108A, Folder 185e)
      - "Abishag", 1923 February 24 (Box 108A, Folder 186)
      - "Black Moon", 1923 July (Box 108A, Folder 187)
      - "Dolced", 1923 November 3 (Box 108A, Folder 188a)
      - "Ethical Dative", 1923 December 1 (Box 108A, Folder 188b)
      - "Golden Calves", 1924 September 20 (Box 108A, Folder 189a)
      - "Sophistication", 1924 October 11 (Box 108A, Folder 189b)
      - "Civilization", 1924 October 18 (Box 108A, Folder 189c)
      - "Love's Simple Tale.", 1924 December 6 (Box 108A, Folder 190)
        See also: box 116, folder 346
      - "Appreciation", 1925 February 7 (Box 108A, Folder 191)
      - "Joao", 1925 April 4 (Box 108A, Folder 192)
      - "Observation", 1925 May 16 (Box 108A, Folder 193a)
      - "The Secret Goddess", 1925 May 30 (Box 108A, Folder 193b)
      - "Gentility", 1925 October 3 (Box 108A, Folder 193c)
      - "Love's Bitter Mystery", 1925 November 7 (Box 108A, Folder 193)
      - "Reunion", 1925 December 12 (Box 108A, Folder 193e)
      - "Splendor and Glory", 1926 January 16 (Box 108A, Folder 193)
      - "The Romantic Hour", 1926 March 20 (Box 108A, Folder 193g)
      - "He Grieved", 1926 May 8 (Box 108A, Folder 193h)
      - "The Last Voltorno", 1926 August 21 (Box 108A, Folder 193i)
      - "Semele", 1926 September 18 (Box 108A, Folder 193j)
      - "Piepowder Court", 1926 October 16 (Box 108A, Folder 193k)
      - "Do and Dare", 1926 November 13 (Box 108A, Folder 193l)
      - "The Public Life", 1926 November 20 (Box 108A, Folder 193m)
      - "Ancestral Voices", 1927 January 22 (Box 108B, Folder 194a)
      - "On Precedent", 1927 March 12 (Box 108B, Folder 194b)
      - "Curly-Tailed Wolf", 1927 April 16 (Box 108B, Folder 194c)
      - "Cramambuli", 1927 May 7 (Box 108B, Folder 195a)
      - "Aesthetics", 1927 June 11 (Box 108B, Folder 195b)
      - "This Very Ancient Song", 1927 October 8 (Box 108B, Folder 196)
      - "The Vulgar Thing", 1927 October 29 (Box 108B, Folder 197a)
      - "The Brutish Person", 1927 November 26 (Box 108B, Folder 197b)
      - "Apotheosis", 1928 March 3 (Box 108B, Folder 198a)
      - "The Grander Casuistry", 1928 March 24 (Box 108B, Folder 198b)
      - "The Philosophy of C. J. S. Smith", 1928 May 5 (Box 108B, Folder 198c)
      - "Cat Act", 1928 May 19 (Box 108B, Folder 199a)
      - "The Noble Nature of Private Waldo Grant", 1928 June 30 (Box 108B, Folder 199b)
      - "Wotan's Child", 1928 August 4 (Box 108B, Folder 199c)
      - "Mother Eglantine", 1928 August 25 (Box 108B, Folder 199)
      - "Americanus Sum", 1928 November 17 (Box 108B, Folder 199e)
      - "Love", 1928 December 15 (Box 108B, Folder 199)
      - "Honor", 1929 January 5 (Box 108B, Folder 199g)
      - "Hexensabbath", 1929 September 7 (Box 108B, Folder 199h)
      - "Sanity", 1929 December 7 (Box 108B, Folder 199i)
      - "Cherries", 1930 March 22 (Box 108B, Folder 199j)
      - "Race", 1930 April 5 (Box 108B, Folder 199k)
      - "Intrusion", 1930 May 10 (Box 108B, Folder 200a)
      - "No Horses, No Beggars", 1930 June 7 (Box 108B, Folder 200b)
      - "The Agreeable Finish", 1930 June 21 (Box 108B, Folder 200c)
      - "The Victorian Blush", 1931 February 14 (Box 108B, Folder 200)
      - "Antipathy", 1931 April 11 (Box 108B, Folder 201)
      - "Manner", 1931 September 26 (Box 108B, Folder 202)
      - "The Feeling For It", 1931 October 10 (Box 108B, Folder 203)
      - "White Man", 1931 October 31 (Box 108B, Folder 204)
      - "Before Breakfast", 1931 November 14 (Box 108B, Folder 205)
      - "A Little Science", 1931 November 21 (Box 108B, Folder 206)
      - "Grandfather Pound", 1931 December 26 (Box 108B, Folder 207)
      - "Erasmus Vincey's Left Foot", 1932 February 6 (Box 108B, Folder 208)
      - "Mnemosyne", 1932 April 30 (Box 108B, Folder 209)
      - "Looking at Things", 1932 July 23 (Box 108B, Folder 210)
      - "The Boy Detectives", 1932 November 12 (Box 108B, Folder 211)
      - "Descendants of Noah Grannis, Master", 1932 December 17 (Box 108B, Folder 212)
      - "Privacy", 1933 January 14 (Box 108B, Folder 213)
      - "Favorite Expedient", 1933 February 11 (Box 108B, Folder 214)
      - "Milk and Honey", 1933 March 4 (Box 108B, Folder 215a)
      - "It Goes Right On", 1933 June 3 (Box 108B, Folder 215b)
      - "The Art of Being Young", 1933 August 12 (Box 108B, Folder 216)
      - "Prominence", 1934 April 7 (Box 108B, Folder 217a)
      - "Duncan Comes Here Tonight", 1934 September (Box 108B, Folder 217b)
      - "Conservation Corps", 1935 March 2 (Box 109, Folder 218)
      - "Be Thou My Good", 1935 September 7 (Box 109, Folder 219)
      - "Triumph", 1935 September 28 (Box 109, Folder 220)
      - "Young Joseph's Good Brethren", 1935 November 23 (Box 109, Folder 221)